<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>[Rep] The Binding of Madou v0.1.2 (Dev)</name>
    <directory>the binding of madou_v0_1_2_dev</directory>
    <id>2964475241</id>
    <description>[h1]&quot;An adventure in basement of a developing magician.&quot;[/h1]
This is a fan-made mod based on [b][i]Madou Monogatari[/i][/b] and [b][i]Puyo Puyo[/i][/b] series, which features 1 new player, 2 new items and 1 new challenge.

This mod is still under development. More new content is planned to be added soon, including collectibles, trinkets, characters, bosses, and story.

The program part of this mod needs to be improved. You are welcome to make suggestions for its improvement.

This mod supports local co-op mode and controller.

This mod has compatibility with [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=836319872]External Item Descriptions[/url] and [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2681875787]Mod Config Menu[/url].
[h2]New character: Arle Nadja[/h2]
[b]▷Starting attributes[/b]
- Health: 3 red hearts
- Speed: 0.9
- Tears: 2.53
- Damage: 3
- Range: 5.5
- Shot Speed: 1
- Luck: 0

[b]▷Starting items[/b]
- Blue grimoire (Pocket active item)
- x20 Mana points

[b]▷Features[/b]
- Level and exp: Killing enemies grants exp points to the player. The player levels up when reaches a certain amount of exp points. When levels up, all red hearts and mana points will be restored, and the player will gain a random stat increase.
- Critical hit: The player has a chance to cause a critical hit when deals damage to enemies. Critical hit deals 200% player's Damage.
- Spells: When holding the Blue Grimoire, the player can held 8 different spells, which will be unlocked if the player reachs a certain level or has certain items or kills cettain bosses. On use, consumes several mp and grants the selected spell effect.

See the documentation named &quot;readme.txt&quot; in mod folder for more detailed information.

[h2]CREDITS[/h2]
Coder:
wither2x

Designers:
Sadship
wither2x

Sprites:
Taoyufei
wither2x

[i]Note: This fan-made mod is not affiliated with SEGA and Sonic Team.[/i]

	</description>
    <version>0.1.2</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Pickups"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Challenges"/>
</metadata>
